const QuizQuest = {
    result:[
    {

        question: "What does the Acronym REST Stand for?",
        correct_answer: "Representational State Transfer",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Representational State Transform",
            "Represent State Transform",
            "Represent State Transfer",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "What is the protocol used in REST?",
        correct_answer: "HTTP",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "FTP",
            "JMX",
            "SOAP",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "What is the HTTP Status Code Related to Page Not Found?",
        correct_answer: "404",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "402",
            "403",
            "401",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "What is the HTTP Code Related to Internal Server Error?",
        correct_answer: "500",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "504",
            "501",
            "502",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "What is the HTTP Code 200 Indicate?",
        correct_answer: "Success",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Error",
            "Completed",
            "Warning",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "Which HTTP method do we use to make an HTTP request to create a new resource?",
        correct_answer: "POST",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "PUT",
            "GET",
            "CREATE",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "Which HTTP method do we use to make an HTTP request to update an existing resource?",
        correct_answer: "PUT",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "POST",
            "UPDATE",
            "DELETE",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "Choose the correct URI format to get a sub-resource by resource id and sub-resource id",
        correct_answer: " /{resource}/{resource-id}/{sub-resource}/{sub-resource-id}",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "/{resource}/{sub-resource}/{sub-resource-id}",
            "{sub-resource}/{sub-resource-id}/{resource}/{resource-id}",
            "/{resource}/{resource-id}/{sub-resource-id}/{sub-resource}",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "Which is not REST Architectural Constraints?",
        correct_answer: "Service orchestration",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Client-Server",
            "Stateless",
            "Cacheable",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "What is the HTTP status code 201 indicate?",
        correct_answer: "Created",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Accepted",
            "No Content",
            "OK",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "What is the HTTP status code 201 indicate?",
        correct_answer: "Created",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Accepted",
            "No Content",
            "OK",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "What is the HTTP status code 201 indicate?",
        correct_answer: "Created",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Accepted",
            "No Content",
            "OK",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "What is the HTTP status code 201 indicate?",
        correct_answer: "Created",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Accepted",
            "No Content",
            "OK",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "Which of the following are terminal operations?",
        correct_answer: "max",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "sorted",
            "Distinct",
            "flatMap",
        ]
    },
    {

        question: "    Which of the following are short-circuit operations?",
        correct_answer: "findFirst",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "reduce",
            "parallel",
            "findNone",
        ]
    },
]
}
export default QuizQuest;
